planoly.com 2018-09-04

# Planoly: Policies - Visually plan and schedule your Instagram posts

_Planogram, Inc., dba Planoly (“Planoly”,”we”, “us” or “our”), is committed to keeping any and all personal information (“Information”) collected from those individuals that visit our website and mobile app (collectively, the “site”) and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Planoly of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards._

This Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Planoly and all of its affiliated websites and mobile applications, including Stylelink.it, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of Planoly you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.

Planoly reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our site homepage at planoly.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy page periodically for any changes.

The provision of Information is contractually required based on your use of the Services. If you do not wish to provide the Information, you may not use the Services.

**_THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS EFFECTIVE AS OF 05/25/2018._**

**CONSENT TO COLLECTION** In order to use Planoly, you must affirmatively consent to our Privacy Policy. Our legal basis for collecting and processing your Information is your explicit consent when accessing the Services and our legitimate interest in website traffic analysis. Please read this Privacy Policy very carefully and contact us (through any of the methods listed in the DATA CONTROLLER INFORMATION section of this Privacy Policy) with any questions.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION  
**We collect the following Information when you use the site:

  * Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you make purchases. You are the source of this Information.
  * Information automatically collected when visiting our site, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies, server logs, and shopping history. You or your device are the source of this Information.
  * Information provided to the site for provision of the services, including information about your brand (“User Content”). You are the source of this Information.
  * Information you provide when requesting customer or technical assistance. You are the source of this Information.
  * If you are a Brand, as defined in the Stylink.it Terms of Service, the following Information for which you are the source:

Information about your goods, services, and websites used for Campaigns (as defined in the Stylelink.it Terms of Service).

    * Information about purchases, returns, and customers.
    * Payment information.
  * If you are an Influencer, as defined in the Stylelink.it Terms of Service: 
    * Information about your social media profiles and presence.
    * Payment information.
    * Information necessary to generate and track Affiliate Links (as defined in the Stylelink.it Terms of Service).

We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.

All photos, videos, and captions uploaded by you belongs to you. We will never use or share your content without your consent.

**PROCESSING AND USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  
**Planoly process and uses Information as follows:

  * To assist in the operation of our site and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request.
  * To process payments.
  * To inform you about new products and services we offer.
  * To send you surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
  * To analyze your use of the site and the types of products and services you prefer.
  * To respond to customer service and technical help requests.
  * To comply with legal requirements.

Planoly does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties. However, Planoly may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personal information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or bankruptcy event. You may opt out of any such transfer if it materially differs from that set forth in this privacy policy.

If you use Stylelink.it, Planoly may use your personal information to track Qualifying Purchases (as defined in the Stylelink.it Terms of Service) and your use of Affiliate Links. Planoly will also use your personal information to process payments and match Brands and Influencers.

Planoly may only otherwise disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

  * Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Planoly and/or our site;
  * Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Planoly; and
  * Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of Planoly and/or the general public.

**USE OF COOKIES  
**The site may use cookies to help process Information. Cookies are small files containing identifying numbers stored on your computer or device. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies. A persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiration date while a session cookie will be deleted at the end of a browsing session. We may use both types of cookies.

You can disable cookies through your web browser or mobile device but doing so may impact your ability to use the site.

We may use cookies and similar software known as web beacons to help count the number of users who have visited our site from certain referral sources. Web beacons collect limited information and do not identify particular individuals. You can block web beacons by disabling cookies.

We may also use Google Analytics to analyze traffic and usage of the site. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. You are encouraged to review Google’s privacy policy at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/

**CHILDREN UNDER AGE OF 13  
**Planoly does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this site.

**UNSUBSCRIBE OR OPT-OUT  
**All users and/or visitors to our site have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our site please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to support@planoly.com.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES  
**Our site may contain links to affiliate and other websites. Planoly does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our site.

**SECURITY  
**Planoly shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.

The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users’ trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.

**RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION  
**Information that we collect will not be kept for longer than is necessary for the relevant processing purpose. We will retain your Information for a minimum period of one day following receipt and for a maximum period of (i) the time you are a user with an account or (ii) ten years, whichever is longer. Notwithstanding the previous sentence, we may retain your Information when such retention is necessary for compliance with legal obligations, the protection of your vital interests, or the vital interests of another person.

You may contact us through any method described in the DATA CONTROLLER INFORMATION section of this Privacy Policy to request any correction, deletion, or copies of your Information. We will comply your requests regarding access, correction, and/or deletion of the Information we store in accordance with any applicable law, including the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

**TRANSFER OF YOUR INFORMATION  
**Planoly is based in the United States, hosts your Information in the United States, and processes your Information in the United States. Transfers of Information to the United States to will be protected by contractual means and prevailing industry standards.

**YOUR RIGHTS UNDER THE EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)  
**We comply with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). The GDPR provides you with the following rights:

  * The Right of Access. You have the right to be informed of, and request access to, the Information we process about you.
  * The Right to Rectification. You have the right to request that we amend or update your personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * The Right to Erasure. You the right to have the Company delete your Information.
  * The Right to Restrict Data. You have the right to request that we temporarily or permanently stop processing your Personal Information.
  * The Right to Object. You have the right to object to us processing your Information on grounds relating to your particular situation or for direct marketing purposes.
  * The Right to Data Portability. You have the right to request a copy of your Information in electronic format and the right to transmit that Information to any other service.
  * The Right not to be Subject to Automated Decision Making. You have the right to not be subject to a decision based solely on automated decision making, including profiling, when such a decision would have a legal effect on you or produce a similarly significant effect.
  * The  Right to Complain: You may file a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority. A list of data protection authorities is available at http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080.

**DATA CONTROLLER INFORMATION  
**The Information we collect and process is controlled by Planogram, Inc., a Delaware (United States) corporation.

You may contact us via email at support@planoly.com to make any request under this Privacy Policy

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our site, please feel free to contact us.
